appsforpcguides.com 2014-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Download Apps for PC

If you need any type of further information or if you have any questions about the privacy policy of appsforpcguides.com then please don’t hesitate to contact us on our official email address at tech.mero[at]gmail[dot]com

Note : Words like “We”, “Us”, “Our” refers to appsforpcguides.com

At appsforpcguides.com, the privacy of our visitors/users/readers is of high importance to us. This privacy policy page gives idea about the types of personal information which is received and collected by appsforpcguides.com and its being used by us.

**Log Files :**

Like so many other web sites over Internet, appsforpcguides.com also makes use of log files. The type of information inside the log files includes various vital data about users like internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider, date and time of visit, referring pages, exit pages.

We even use and analyze clicks of users over our website to analyze trends, track visitor’s behaviors and demographic information.

IP address or any information received  and collected by log files do not include anything which is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies And Web Beacons

appsforpcguides.com does use cookies to store vital information about visitor’s/reader’s/visitor’s preferences, it helps to record information like on which type of pages the visitor access or visit the most.

It customizes web pages contact based on visitor’s browser type, version and other demographic preferences and all type of other information and data that the visitor sends via their Internet Browser like Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, etc.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, does use cookies to serve advertisements on appsforpcguides.com as we are published at Google Adsense Program
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables them to serve advertisements to visitors, readers, users to appsforpcguides.com and other websites on the Internet.
  * Our readers, visitors, users can opt out of the use of the DART Cookie by visiting this official page on content network privacy policy by Google ad, please visit this link : <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

We have also partnered with other advertising networks which may use cookies as well as web beacons on appsforpcguides.com, those partners include: Google Adsense, Infolinks, Chitika, Yahoo-Bing Ad Media.

All these third-party ad networks use technology to show advertisements on our website and the links that appear on appsforpcguides.com send directly to your Internet Web browsers. They receive or collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address when any advertisement is shown on our website to your browsers. Some other type of technology like cookies, JavaScript and Web Beacons may also be used by these third-party advertisements partners so that they can analyse the effect of advertisements or to serve more personalized ads for our readers, visitors, users.

appsforpcguides.com has no type of access or control over these cookies that are received and collected by other third-party ad networks. If user wants, then he/she can opt out of these cookies partially or fully in one particular location from here : [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

If you need, you should always consult the respective privacy policies of these Third-Party Ad networks for more in-detail information about their practices, information and other instructions about these cookies. We can’t control the activities of those third-party Ad Networks with whom we have partnered.

If you want to deactivate cookies, you can do so by your own Internet Browser Options. You can find information on how to disable cookies on specific browsers on their respective websites.
